<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SoftwareShop</string>
    <string name="MainLogo">softwareShopLogo</string>
    <string name="company_name">SoftwareShop Limited</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="office_address">4, Pepple Street, Fki Plaza, Beside Zenith Bank, Ikeja, Lagos.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="overview_body">A leading provider of INTEGRATED Information Technology Solutions for businesses across several industries ,Founded in 2001 just from a spot on the street of Otigba computer village and within a short time, We grew to a kiosk registered as Media Centre in 2004 Head Office at No 7,Otigba Street, and by 2013 Softwareshop Limited was registered with CAC in Nigeria, following year 2014 a foreign branch was opened in South-Africa registered with CIPRO as Softwareshop (PTY) LTD. fully in operation in South-Africa Central Business District, commonly called Johannesburg CBD. Softwareshop has since transformed from a vendor company into a research and application design, develop and full Technology HUB, also a solution provider to numerous sectors across Africa...focusing on Artificial intelligence, training and empowerment, we have added Cvhub4Africa LTD and SoftwareshopHUB LTD to help us achieve this aim.</string>
    <string name="overview_header">Who are we?</string>
    <string name="vision_head">Our Vision</string>
    <string name="vision_body"><![CDATA[Limited to become a leader in Complete Technology Services, Integration and Consultancy provision that turns client’s challenges into The main vision of Softwareshop extraordinary successes.\n\n\nREINVENT THE SIMPLICITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY BUSINESS ACCROSS AFRICA.\n\nWe aim to deliver the most secure and user-friendly information Technology, that truly serves individuals and businesses, Marketplace & FinTech. We have made significant investment in dedicated warehousing /processing facilities, information systems, sales and marketing channels, diagnostic and repair equipment, technical people and training, and both partner web sites. Accordingly, Softwareshop Limited is recognized by major IT giants.]]></string>
    <string name="mission_body"><![CDATA[We intend to be a customer‐centric company that is dedicated to leveraging emerging technologies to provide the highest level of quality products and services, customer service, and security to improve our client’s business. Softwareshop Limited deals in a range of software products that support different business processes and functions. We sell Genuine software and also beat any verified price. Softwareshop Limited offers installation, configuration & training services for all the software applications we sell/support. We will also offer a FREE consulting advice on which software features match your business requirements.]]></string>
    <string name="mission_head">Our Mission</string>
    <string name="visit_our_website">Visit Our Website</string>
</resources>
